{
    "subject": "Elmar_Klos",
    "predicate": "created",
    "object": "The_Shop_on_Main_Street",
    "human_readable": "Elmar Klos created The Shop on Main Street.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.7519526481628418,
            "question": "Who created the movie The Shop on Main Street?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6161108613014221,
            "question": "Where was The Shop on Main Street filmed?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5814399719238281,
            "question": "What year was The Shop on Main Street released?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5808089375495911,
            "question": "What are some themes explored in The Shop on Main Street?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5625483393669128,
            "question": "What genre is The Shop on Main Street?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.45394206047058105,
            "question": "What is the title of the film Elmar Klos made?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4038337767124176,
            "question": "What kind of work did Elmar Klos do?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.36907875537872314,
            "question": "Is The Shop on Main Street a novel or a movie?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3661247491836548,
            "question": "Did The Shop on Main Street win any awards?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.15386365354061127,
            "question": "Can you tell me about a film directed by Elmar Klos?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Elmar Klos created The Shop on Main Street.",
            "html": "yago_8480_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Did The Shop on Main Street win any awards?",
            "html": "yago_8480_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Is The Shop on Main Street a novel or a movie?",
            "html": "yago_8480_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What kind of work did Elmar Klos do?",
            "html": "yago_8480_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "yago_8480_15.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_8480_22.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_8480_27.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_8480_35.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_8480_43.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_8480_57.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_8480_62.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_8480_67.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_8480_78.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_8480_8.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the evaluation of the triple:\n\n```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nExplanation:\n\nThe documents mention that \"Shop on the Main Street\" is a Czechoslovak film by directors Jan Kad\u00e1r and Elmar Klos. However, they do not provide any information about Elmar Klos creating The Shop on Main Street, but rather that he was one of the directors of the movie."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents mention that the film \"Shop on Main Street\" was directed by Jan Kad\u00e1r and Elmar Klos. Therefore, it is accurate to state that Elmar Klos created \"The Shop on Main Street,\" as he was one of the directors of the film."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "mistral-nemo": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "-",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}